Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love You erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
Tell me how I'm...
Mystical yo welcome to the madness buckle in tight
And slay the dead
Dance like you're awake, hands don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sides twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame this ain't your mama's podcast this a runaway train
Boom, set into the night.
Panel looking sideways, someone's gotta fight.
Producers on mute, praying this don't spike.
Diamonds feeling spicy, shirts slipping down low.
Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣa Ṣ
kien tatzilinu minara kelecha hamalata pahadbura pahatila leolme olamim. Amen.
Okay, okay, okay guys, wow.
Wow, you like AI music? I do too. I think it's pretty cool. Actually, I did most of the writing of those and you know
Love the direction of it. But yes, very assisted by the AI
No, uh, no shame in my game guys. No shame in my game. I
Just want to address a few things. Okay
Wow, it's like oh, it's a little bit different like being able to actually speak and not have like five people
Plus a whole chat of people just hating on me. You know, oh he ran he ran. Well, it's like, you know what?
I'm wearing headphones. It's loud. It's loud in my ear. I don't want to hear
Screaming at the top of the I have to scream and it might not my throat hurts. Okay
It's so interesting. Wow. Why is it, I mean, it's like, yeah, there's a different victim
every day, I guess, in the panel verse, right? A new sacrificial goat. It's called a scapegoat.
It's actually called a scapegoat. Actually, I'm a cow perform. So I'm used to, yeah, wow,
wow, yeah. I'm used to being scapegoated, right? It's okay. Guys and mods, please do not hide anybody
You know three days like I said hate take your hatred out on me. I want it
I want to hear I want to hear all the hatred go ahead. Tell me everything you think about
I'm not gonna have one person hidden mods put down your wrenches tonight
Buddy trolling. Yeah. Mmm. Nice nice to have a buddy troll, huh? Anyway
Be the beat is the least of my words I love you like I said
I mean, I love all I love most of these people right to my detriment. I don't know. I don't know why it's like
I'm constantly abused by them
Constantly called out of my name constantly. I'm doing something wrong, right? I'm do I'm the I'm
Apparently so evil because I have different ideas of how to make money from the show. I'm grasping at straws. Obviously. It's like, you know
No one's really donating. It's like what what it's like
So I come up with new ideas
Like oh and then it but it then it's like oh if someone donates, you know five dollars
Six months ago to kick off flurry diamond off the panel. I
Oh, I apparently owe them my life. I owe them my total respect
Oh, this person has helped me so much this person. That's calling me scammer grifter
Like I did I take flurry diamond off the panel for five minutes? Yeah, I didn't scam them
If I've saved, you know, have I messed up?
Maybe I think three times maybe where it's like, yeah, I brought someone on the panel
Maybe they've been kicked off. Did I refund the money every time? Yes
I mean, it's like jeez
I mean it does but it's like they're all
It's a mob mentality, right? It's a mob mentality where it's like, okay, let's all oh look weakness like you know
Let's go go like sharks in on this person. So anyway
I never
Took any money out of a bank account, you know, somebody else's bank account. I never brought so somebody's purse
Everything was consensual. It's like, oh, well this person said that my kid am I responsible for everything my dominators say no
Right. Yeah, playing the victim again the bull, but it's fine guys. You can leave that person there
You that person there those I just want them to reveal themselves. Please. Please just look to reveal themselves
Right
Guys and you know, maybe people are people make sure I'm held accountable, but you know
There's a I don't think I remember a time that I was not
Totally open. I don't I don't know and very very few people have even had like every time every donation
That has been requested or refund up, you know
That I have not
Performed
Like I said, I would I refunded. I mean, it's like so why is why is it bad to be monetized?
Do you expect me to sit here?
Every day
and put all my time, energy, all my thoughts, spending
money on StreamYard, money on the show.
Like I put everything into the show, everything.
It's like I didn't have money for the show
to begin with, I did the first,
I don't think I had like a dollar donation for a few months,
you know, I got monetized.
people are people are welcome to join the membership I know and it's like well
and it's like really distasteful to talk about other people's monetary did I
ever go on anybody's channel say don't do it to this person this you know even a
person I hated I was like if this is on purpose to this is like I'm gonna be is
Just so there isn't a hint of
Any kind of disparity or whatever. I've I purposely
Let my enemies promote their shows on here. I can go to some of my enemies chats not enemies
I don't even consider my vacancy or me their enemy. I can go to some of their chats. I
Can see a lot of people I've introduced them, you know, and they can say you know, I guess that they consider me their enemy
Maybe they did promote me at one time
So it's certainly not anymore, but
You know, I haven't asked I haven't that's why this is why I avoid panels, but you know, I love beta and so I
Went on a panel you can guys if you watch the episode you can watch it
You know, you can't see it now, but you can probably watch it soon
on rumble
You can see my attitude coming into the show now is like I want to go on and have fun
I want to go on and love on people. I want to go on and make up with people. I want to go on and like
Work things out and it turns out like this it turns out like this I
Can't have I can't have any email donating to my show
Instantly gets called gay
And it's like not easy for like a lot of straight guys to be called because there's not a lot of gay men on the panel or on the channel
Right. I'm the biggest, you know queer here, right?
so instantly
They get called. Oh, you want to suck on his dick? You're sucking his dick. Oh, you fuck
You know, it's like a minus. We'll just you know called FHGOT, right?
Okay, I'll do a mass on banning
Let's just do a mass on banning again, I'm gonna unban everybody
Okay
There's not gonna be one ban person. I'm also gonna unmod everybody and so don't take it personally guys
I'll have to mod for myself for a little while
It's not personal. It's gonna be everybody. So it applies to everybody. There's not gonna be one mod
Not one mod. Okay, and don't don't be offended. Don't be offended. I love and I love people that have done a great job
I appreciate you
There's too much going on right now with the people that I consider my friends my mods this
attacking me. It's on a good look, you know?
But I go in things like I'm not trying to like say I'm a great I'm the best person I'm like I'm
but I do I'm a loving person I'm also really sensitive and
Just having people yell and scream at me and accuse me all all night. And it's like, you know, even towards the friends, you know
So you can say I'm like whining about it or whatever whatever you want to say
That's one mod everybody
I'm sorry, you know, I'll probably be remodeling people as time goes on
Not anything about anything all it is is like
I have people that I love and trust as mods
Well, I'm not even a mod for you because you do this and this it's like and I put up
I put up with it. I put up with it
Yeah, my mods talking shit about me tonight. I'm in my own chat to me sometimes
Okay
But I love you guys, but and I okay nightbot will stay a mod everybody else. I'm so sorry
It's nothing personal against anybody. Okay?
It's just I have to the nightbot will remain a mod. Okay. I
Made people mods. I've told them go do it. You want to do like these mod people have just
Okay, some of you have been great mods, I love so many of you
Okay, I just have to make it fair or else, you know, I'm not fair
Just taking everybody out of this community community thing everybody. I love everybody
So don't don't be offended this is for right now, this is a temporary thing, okay
It just must be done
It must be done. Okay, so everybody is going to be unhidden
Unmodded please do not take offense
We'll talk about it we'll talk about it
Don't know
Wow, gay holocaust, I just saw on my screen, wow, what communities am I in, what have
I done, gay holocaust, someone just put that, it's from a channel, okay, guys, okay, but
guys, just understand, I think personal against anybody, most of you don't.
I don't know I just need to do that now because I don't know who I can trust sometimes I
Love you guys. I love all of you. Okay. It's just the sewer slide
Bating what does that mean sewer slide baiting?
Go ahead. Well explain what that means. Can you explain what that means?
What is sewer slide baiting mean?
The bull let me know everybody's by the way been on hidden
It's a free-for-all, okay
Take I want I want to see all the hate today. I want to see who hates me why go ahead
So if you have you have anything to say you can say to me, right?
Everybody everybody is on band. Do you know you hear everybody miss the 24-7 lives? Yeah
Well, you know, obviously
If no one's gonna
You know, I'm gonna put 24-7 in my life, but I'm not allowed to make money
I'm not allowed to ask for money, right? You don't want me to be attacked. Well, I don't know if you saw what just happened
It's
It's hard like so many times this week. I was like and people you know people make fun of me
Oh, you're crying. You're crying. I'm not crying guys. I'm not crying. I cried when my father passed away. I
cried when like
My cat died today. I was told oh you let your cat get eaten by a coyote
At least beta takes care of her cats. You know, you know, you know, you let your cat get eaten by a coyote
Yeah, I can control the forces of nature where I can control
You know, I have like, you know several cats they can go inside outside. I give my cats freedom
I think they'll have a happier life. You know, I have a small apartment
And so
I let them come in and out if they please
You know, and yeah, it's maybe I've had a cat. I've got a couple cats or one cat get hit by a car
I've had a cat eaten by a coyote and some cats. I don't know what happened what happened. It's just like
Basically proofs of fiction basically just like
Get a oh that person. Oh, I mean every just imagine like everybody
screaming at you like
Like I don't know
I really haven't seen this happen to anybody else like and I watch a lot of YouTube
um
I have been
grateful I've been thankful I
I give I give too much freedom because then it's like this person's happy this person's not happy this person
I tried to do my best
I've been here every day this year guys every every I mean it's like I miss two days
I think there's been two days this year where I haven't like
You know gotten part of the camera
No matter how I looked oh
Now people are saying oh, I look so skinny. Well, because I've been wearing t-shirts, right?
You didn't notice I used to wear flannels like every day. That's my worst t-shirts now
I'm skinny. I've always been a skinny and show you many pictures of myself
Throughout the years been the same way
It's okay
And I'm not like I'm not mad at it because it's like this is just a sad thing about human nature, right?
It's like I
Don't know I don't want to say it's jealousy
Or anything I don't know what there's to be jealous of if I'm so terrible
It's like what I mean, it's like just leave me alone. It's like you hate me so much
It's like so much hate
It's hard and I can turn it into like other stuff I can like
Alchemize it right I can turn it into a good situation, but it's like I people should some people should know me some people should know me well enough
Do you think I support racism? Do you think I support homophobia? Do you think I support at hate or sexism?
you know I try to
Protect people and it's like I maybe I didn't do that great of a job at it before maybe I have my times
you know gone for the drama and the
you know, but it's these communities. It's like, this is how they talk a lot of these people.
It's like, am I supposed to just kick off everybody? Am I supposed to like, if I have like,
you know, one donator left, am I supposed to like, throw them away and say, oh, well, you know,
you said, you cut, you said the word, but it's like everybody's saying this shit. I don't know.
Um, I think I get pretty much the worst of it, right?
On my show they're like, oh, yeah, I get this too. I get this too. You get so you get to call it you get
People every day that are saying you're dying of AIDS
Get that every day, you know, I don't know you get every day
You're just like so I'm not gonna I'm not gonna like bitch about it like why about I understand
I came into it like this up. Did I ask for it? No, I
Wanted to have a fun show
Can I control who comes to the show and not?
Yes, and no you can you can't it's like no you can't really because anybody can come to each
It's a it's like YouTube, so it's like unless I like
You know put everything on members only a private
Then what will I have nobody?
I'll just be sitting alone
So I try to like monetize the hate I just guys I did my best
Every day I'm here
Every day even and I've been feeling like such shit lately like I've been like it's been so hard. That's like I
But I don't know I don't care. I don't care what you say about me, you know
But
At the end of the day I'm human being I'm not perfect
And I do believe like everybody else. I'm not just this person that's like, oh, uh-huh
It's like especially when people are calling me out of my name
now
Did I did I disrespect anybody like personally like they've disrespected me like I mean, it's like you know
I've given it back to some people
I've given I've mirrored some people some people. I've mirrored them, right?
I'll chat it seems to hate is what it stands for yeah
Isn't that sad and it's like and maybe it's gonna be good if I get like you know
If everyone just like leaves like not everybody, you know, there's some people that like are good people that like me
But it's like most people
Just hate me and are here just to like ruin the show and like to come try to porn bomb me
I get porn bombs, you know, almost every day
And we're bombed
Shows I have to delete the hours long show just like all this work you put into it
In my fault for like letting people on right I'm like I want to do a panel show I like I like panels like you know
It's like just sick
Don't know. I don't know if you see how vicious it is and maybe it's like you can say oh, he's just whining
He's clean so low cow
Low cow just like laugh at him. Well, you know cows cows need grass. Okay, so if I'm a low cow
Why are you starving me? Why are you starving me to death if I'm a low cow? Why are you starving me?
The people that call me that's not not everybody. I'm saying people that call me a low cow
Well, are you giving me grass so you can give me or you're just trying to take some milk?
right
If you're gonna fucking you're gonna like, you know, just like
Try to like you massacre me and take all my meat and milk
Might as well pay the butcher for it, right?
No, you just repeat what?
No, no, no, I I should just be doing everything for free. I should not have any monetized
No, no matter that I got the idea from the system from them, right?
No matter no matter. No, no, no, I I'm not allowed to do it. They are they are I'm not allowed to do it, but
Right, it's a panelist it's a I mean, it's like and I understand it's it's like it gets but people kind of know what they're in for in that regard because
The community is very similar along some of these lines, but am I an attacker? No. Have I
Put up with people guys. Do you see how many people like kick off?
I take the backstage and if I put people backstage, oh you put them back sit. Oh my god, and it's like and I have mods
Oh, we'll bring them back bring them back bring them back. We like this person. We like this person
We like this person like I think well this person is like saying terrible things about me, but
With the audience once you know, I do I do care with the audience once right?
I never attacked anybody like like some of these are my supposed to be my friends right and they are attacking me
They're they're fine with people calling me grifter. They're fine with people calling me scam artists
They're fine with people saying I have HIV. They're like, well, you know, I
Got called a whore one time. I got told my punani smells. Well, you know, it's like I
Yeah, I get
Everything has been all those things have been said. I'm not my punani, but you know, oh, I'm just a filthy
disgusting drug
AIDS HIV you're stupid dumb like retarded am I that dumb? I mean it's like
so
I signed up for you sign up for I
Didn't sign up just to be abused. It's like, you know
There's panelists on other show. I don't know you guys know I'm talking about
First thing I did when I as soon as I could I got this computer
So I can improve the show the first thing I did actually I got a loan for it
Okay, I got a loan for I got a loan for it so I could do this right?
So I could get it
And it was for you it was for you guys
It's all I have it all set up I I'll set up for the show
The VR doesn't work and everything it's like all all the matters is the cameras working the streamers working
I'm able to go on easier.
Right, quite he-man, but I'm not gonna, like, dilute myself.
I mean, I'm not gonna do two shows.
I mean, imagine that now I can do two shows without getting paid for, right?
And fill up another channel and shit like that, right?
No.
I'm not going to separate it.
The show is what the show is going to be.
The show is like freedom.
It's like freedom to come on the panel.
It was supposed to be, you know, come on the panel, talk to me.
I went into my self-knowing, my Aquarius thing, right?
Similar, but at least he got, I mean,
he makes half a billion dollars, you know,
and puts up a less drama than I've had on the show lately,
right?
People don't even want me to make $10 like $5 send up like $1 like they get mad over $1, right? Oh
My god
You're donated every donator gets attacked. I'm sorry. That's not you know guys don't even if you want to donate
You can just do this do um the cash app and I'll keep it anonymous because I don't want people getting attacked for donating to me
I'm sorry if you have been and it's like it's a shame too
Who would do that? Like I don't even see that happen on any other channel. It's always okay, you know
Just don't know like why is like I'm the exception, but then again, I'm a capricorn. I am
Capricorns are notorious for being scapegoated if you're a capricorn when you know, you know, right?
Literally the goat the scapegoat, okay?
It's like, I'm blamed for the drama in the panel, right?
I'm blamed, like, or anything bad that happens.
And anything that's said to anybody, it's my fault.
If I didn't, you know, I don't want to bitch,
I don't want to bitch, hold on.
I just want, hold on, no, I can't.
But I, but I, but I really did, I went on the show, I went on that show, my friend's
show, like I consider my best friend, okay, my best friend, who I would like do anything
for.
I would do anything for her.
I don't have many friends. So that's my best friend. She doesn't even like me. You know when
No, I don't I can't play content because it's like I'll just get
If it was me playing content
You guys know like I would just be instantly like, you know, copyright strike. Oh, you know, it's like any you know
I'm not allowed to
Share con I can barely I'm afraid to use my content sometimes, you know. Oh, well, I'm in the clip
I'm gonna be dog your dogs
It's hard. It's not easy. I mean it's like and you think other people that run panels and they're like
Oh, we're just doing this for fun fun. This is what you can think is fun. I
Have so much fun on the show, but is it like also like the hardest thing I've ever done in my life. Yes
Is it the saddest thing have I been hurt more on the show than if I'm bullied more hated more
No, then any me time in my life
It's not all fun. It's not all fun and games. It's a lot of work a
Lot of energy. I poured myself into this at the end of the day. I'll have this
I'll have my I'll have my show off the show
No, I'll have these episodes on you know
That'll be it. That's this is it. This is my this isn't my life
like
It's not just fun for me. It's my life
So it's serious and it gets scary sometimes. I can't and I'm not allowed to share. Well, I'm like really
struggling right now
You know, please help because if I I did that once. Oh my god, he's begging for food
He's begging for food. He's begging for this. Oh, he's back be better. I mean, it's like
It's like I'm not allowed to
So I have to you know, I always have to put on a good face and be strong and
You know, sometimes I fade into the background by the way guys, you know
I'm sorry if I'm like I
Heard anybody's feelings or anything, but I don't mean to
Not mad. I'm not
Crying, you know, I'm not crying. There's not a tear. I'm not wearing these glasses. I'm crying. Okay. Oh, right. I'm not
I don't cry, my, the only thing I would cry for is like a life, you know?
Unfortunately, I've had to cry for some lives, you know?
Like, lives, like, you know, people lose their life.
And that's just me missing people, right?
Or like one of the people back.
Swat magic people
Yeah, you're talking about Goetia then right but it's like I know Goetia though. I'm not afraid of Ziggy. I
Don't the thing about Goetia is like there's
ways of
Like first of all not all the great goetic demons are demons. You know some of them are
They're kind of demigods or deeds, you know, they're they're not all them are evil. Some of them are just demonized, right?
Right, right. Okay. Yeah
so
But it's like the yeah, yeah, he's in this swamp, right, but
when you're dealing with like someone that
The higher ones, you know, it's not
Not it's hard to explain I can't really talk about it here because
People will be like, what the fuck is he talking about?
The Goetia, first of all, is flawed because it's like it treats the demons like, you know, or you have to
bind them, chain them and order them instead of like
Talk to them
Hear their side of the story listen to them
Find out like the truth. It's about oh, I want to make you know some money
Had a word why find the treasure?
Right, it's like it's people you know, so that's it's a good different
It depends on your intention. It depends on
basically
your heart
So there's a really good quote I saw recently and it says the truth is revealed to those only to those
With a certain thing
The truth right and that's a like a loving heart right kind of simple me see black RG. It's my channel
I know but it goes to Yumi. It's like what Yumi all I saw all I know about Yumi is like she's like this nice Indonesian lady
I mean, I don't I hardly know her like you know, I meet people on the panel Yumi. I like what I
Don't really I'm not really in the chat like that and it's like she was just hi. How are you psyche? How I miss her psyche?
How are you today? You know, are you okay? You know, that's all I hear. I don't see like
the racism and maybe that the racist she was racist in some chat to somebody and
then with like when I finally did see it in mind it's like okay well yeah guys I
get like thousands and thousands of comments you know in the comment section
I can't and I'm trying to run the show and it's hard to keep track of everything
okay so
All I saw was like she's getting attacked in this chat. I'm getting attacked
She's been telling me these people are the flying monkeys then they're literally on their show
It has a circus tent wings a monkey and a circus set
Oh, here's the flying monkeys and they're proud of it
And they they they're not only most flying monkeys wouldn't have the gall to actually say I'm a flying monkey, right?
These do you know, that's the kind of flying monkeys there. They're proud to be flying monkeys. They're public flying monkeys. They're they're
Promoting that they're flying monkeys. Okay, so I'm like, okay, she's right about that. I see her being attacked. I
Was fine with her
But it's like how can I how can I micromanage?
Everybody I can't
guy
What is up watching for what you me and ghost influence buying influence
Well, you know at the time ghost donated
Nobody else was really donating and I was actually able to like have my best month ever on the on YouTube
I don't know. It's like it's kind of like
You know, it's kind of like a
By influence well
Try to buy some influence. I don't know. It's like you really you don't really have to buy influence
It's like you can be influential. It's like just like today spunky says take this person off
I take the person off the person was a member. It's spunky a member. I don't know. I don't think so
It's spunky donated. Yes. She has spunky has donated, but um, that I wasn't really thinking about
Or remembering that but yeah, she did she bought me some cool stuff. I mean
But these are donators. So guys, you know like like a college, right?
And a college will have donators and sometimes the college will like
Let the person's kids in because
They're actually supporting
So people actually support the show. I mean black rg. Have you donated a penny?
I mean, it's like or become a member or anything. It's like
I'm gonna like if people are actually supporting me putting food in my mouth
They don't deserve like a like a little like recognition from me. They don't deserve to at least they get their money's worth
I don't want to like say
Oh, well you gave it. Oh, you get you donated. Well, then you can't it's like
Yeah, I don't know I have it. I have systems if they over donate and stuff like that. Maybe I'll I don't know but
You have actually what but you have actually what what?
You'd like me to give me good advice
Yeah, I remember you black RG like when you helped me out at that time, but I remember other stuff too, right?
Before it is you don't have to do it. I would have you on the panel
I mean, I didn't have you on the panel one night because you're like kind of kind of harp on me, right?
You have I had no idea
Black RG
Well
I
Could donate a penny a penny to somebody I could I could donate $1 super chat for the rest of that person's life
I'll say I'm a donator. I'm a donator, right?
It's not really about the donator or stuff like that. I have a service. I provide the service
You know, I try to make it fair, right? So
You put you go buy something
No, you get something in return usually, right? Or else what I'm gonna be considered. All right. It says no win situation, right?
Okay, let's have a talk
Hold on very careful today very careful
It's me
I'm not gonna porn ball. All right. There you go. No, the reason why I wanted to come up the other day
And you wouldn't let me on is you looked I was just I was not looking at
No, you looked absolutely horrible your eyes were bugged out of your head
You were rocking back and forth you were talking very you had very paranoid thoughts
And you you were completely bugging out and people were trying to manipulate you at the same time
You actually had me worried which is why I came off
I don't know what that was all about if it's lack of sleep or maybe whatever it was you didn't look healthy
As far as your channel goes like you can have people, you know donate large amounts and have
Influenced over your stream, but you know people are gonna choose not to watch I came here
Listen, it's your channel do run it the way you want to run it
Why are you bugging out on me? What the fuck did I do to you? I'm just trying to have a conversation with you
I'm not attacking you in any way. Well, first you came up saying, oh, your bars were broken out. You look all bare and blah blah blah
No, you didn't look healthy that day. I came up because I was worried about you like legitimately
You know, all right, you know what? You don't want help. You don't want people to look out for you
That's fine. You could keep doing what you're doing because it's working out fantastic later
Well, that's really helpful. I mean, that's very, really helpful advice. You know, if you don't like the show, if you don't want to donate, don't. I mean, it's like...
Yeah, exactly. Hey, Charisma.
Samantha, not trying to help. Not trying to help. He's not trying to help.
He's not, he's not a lover of psyche, okay?
He's not, not a, please, I mean, come on.
You couldn't have the conversation,
maybe not the right time, RG,
maybe work on your timing and with that, you know?
When I come up, I had you up, you know,
you were able to talk, you kicked yourself off.
I was going to talk. I was willing to talk. I'm not kicking anybody off or anything. I'm letting everybody up
These just I
Don't know RG. I
Don't know
Super helpful though. I'm not really looking for help or anything. I'm just like
Expressing myself right now not looking for like oh, oh someone else is gonna have the answer
I have the answers for myself. Okay. Let me just do my thing. I'm okay, and I am running my show like I want to do
Okay, whatever. I mean Jesus Christ
I mean of all people of all people. Oh, I mean, I'm here to help. Oh, what a helper. Thank you so much. Thank you so much
Sure, but whatever you're gonna say was gonna be super helpful. Sure
Yeah, did I ask? Yeah, did I ask? Oh, I need I need to I need to I need the answer
No, I know the answer. The answer is just I'm being attacked for like basically no reason
I'm being pushed into a corner people screaming at me
right
How about like someone to listen, okay, how about someone to listen? That's what I'm looking for right now
I'm not looking for the answer. I know the answers. Okay
It's not like I'm asking for advice when you say I don't know what to do. Well, I don't know what to do
Okay, well, maybe I don't know. Maybe I'm sounding helpful. So whatever. I know what to do. I know what to do. I
Know what to do, which is what I'm doing. I'm learning my show. I'm talking. This is what the show is
I'm running a show. So I don't need to be told what to do. That's the thing
I don't like to be told what to do or what I need to do or that kind of thing. That's the problem in the first place
I know it. I know I'm doing my thing
The problem is getting attacked.
Didn't blow you okay?
Let's see.
That's just like...
That's always behind it, right?
Just blow me now.
Okay.
Yeah.
Anyway, I was willing to have a conversation
and have people give their opinions and stuff like that,
but I don't need to be told what to do.
I'm doing fine. I'm actually doing fine.
Okay.
Man, this pot sucks.
I like charisma.
I'm just expressing myself and I'm but I'm allowing you to if you want to hate on me go ahead and hate on me like
You know, I was I'm not going to kick out anybody for hating on me. Just like stay within the to s and stuff like that
But I really want people to think why are you hating on me? Like what is it about me that is?
Making everybody like
Lip, I mean it's like
I really went into like you can watch the episode you can watch the episode you can see I was having so much fun like a couple hours ago
I was like
Laughing we were all laughing the chat was laughing. I was you know stripping and it was just like it's fun
That's what it's about. It's not about like
Just
Hate
He was coming from a good place. Maybe it's just like, like I said, it's like the timing. I'm like, I'm not, I don't want to be told. Oh, you look like this. You look like that. You're bugging out. You're bugging out. You know, it's like, no, like, and I know these are local farmers that are like doing this stuff. Right.
Lot of people are these local farmers see me as some joke, right?
I'm here to make you laugh. I'm here to entertain. I'm here to like
facilitate
Conversations and have fun. It's just like it's just like why can't people just have fun. I
Want to have fun. It's like I want to
Good conversation. Yeah, people just get me so wrong. It's like it's like I feel so misunderstood
And it's like are you guys watching? I'm here like every day for hours, you know
Expressing myself and that's like I still you don't you don't know me
Don't know like you don't really like you don't like
See that I'm like not a monster
I like to see the good in everybody. I like to try to find the good in everybody and I'm not mad at anybody
And I say I'm not even mad at OG or whatever
Like it was just like I just not in the mood to like be lectured about what I'm doing wrong and blah blah blah
Am I doing something wrong? I don't think so
I think I'm doing like a lot of stuff right. I'm actually this was my best my best month. It's like
People that get me will get me people that won't they won't I just want to like basically say
You just hate me. Do you hate me?
Why are you here
It's fun to hate somebody that's your entertainment is like, oh, I hate this person so much. Let me go
Spoil their day. Let me go ruin their chat. Let me go ruin the hate me that much
What did I ever do to you?
Did I do something to anybody?
Like I'm really just trying that's what I'm trying to figure out somebody has the answer to that. What did I do to you?
Rather than just people with their opinions about like, you know, this and this they don't like this. They don't like this
What did I do to you?
I'm here for like
What why does Emma have a channel and she's allowed to kick out who she wants and she's allowed to
Have her mods take out people and you know her mods listen to her and like like her
And then it's like if I ask my mom to do something. It's like they don't like
Well, you just change your mind. Well, I can change my mind about later
It's not it's like and it's like I appreciate the good mods and stuff like that
But it's like that people are begging any mods and it's like and people take it so seriously
And they don't even do a good job for me. I get some people do some people do but it's like
Wow
How about if you'd like me I need to find my audience. I need to find my real audience
It's just like I just what is this like just like trying to like destroy me
Really, that's what I want to know
I've got I watched I mean, I I don't really participate that much in other panels, but I'm
I'm there, you know, and I see stuff and that's like and I see what said and I see how some people you know
And some people are treated unfairly, but at least they have like
And I do have good people. I do have good people, but it's like in the good people, too
It's like they'll they'll like I don't know if the people realize I don't like to be told what to do. I
Don't like to be harped on it's like and it's like oh
How much just like
Follow my lead the work with me. Like why is it always a fight like?
That's the questions I want to know not not not what is going on like that. I mean, I do have questions
But it's like do I really?
Am I gonna get the answer? I mean, I know the answer. I'm sorry. I'm gonna get I know what answers
Yeah, and it's like then there's people like you know, you know, it's like
I have a guest on this sometimes the guests will be controversial maybe people hate the guests sometime
But it's like yeah, that's when it's like, you know if they come up and you can come up and have it out with them
It's like oh ban this person ban this person. They don't don't have this person in the show
Don't have this person the show. They did this they did this. It's like I'm not gonna go
Research everybody's criminal record. I'm not gonna go
Look at what they you know if they you know spit on their you know kindergarten teacher and stuff like that
I mean, it's like this is not really not part of it's like I'm just here to like so
I don't I don't know everybody's background some people I know better than others
But it's like
And it's like oh, yeah, just run your show, but yeah, but then it's like
You know people will just like come on just more attack I don't know
Yeah
But guys, thank you for letting me express myself
Thank you for letting me express myself and just you know, I'm not here to like you know cry for hours and whatever and it's like, you know, it's just
You don't like me
Leave me alone, okay, don't come to the show
Don't don't don't it's like I'm looking for an audience of
People that at least like me right at least like like me or at least respect me
Right, oh, I'm disrespecting myself. I'm doing the blah blah blah. No, it's like that people that will say that are
disrespecting me, okay, I
Am respecting myself. I'm taking care of myself. I'm alive. I'm 44 years old. I'm a grown adult. I'm
You know, it's like it's just too much hate. It's scared your people have scared away every every new person that comes in
Every donator every person that shows me any kindness. Oh
Go suck on his dick. Go suck psyche's dick more right anybody that says hey, you know, you're okay like you go fucking suck his dick
That's what I'm talking about
Yeah, we try this again
Please okay. I'll just listen. I'm just gonna listen you talk. Well, no, I'm not gonna put you down or anything
Like and the only reason why I brought up the other day is because you said I didn't allow you on panel
And I and I was just telling you the reason why I came up, you know
It could have been anything you just maybe you were sick that day and didn't feel well. That's all it wasn't a tax
Okay
And this you me broad she's in here under an all she's a very strange person
Very very strange and she's starting a lot of trouble
And I've noticed a lot of people that come from the people's podcast
Kind of try to use your platform to start shit with other communities, right? I don't know if that's true or not true, right?
Because your your panel seems to be a melting pot of different communities, right? And not everyone's gonna get along
All right, what's what's the matter? Why why you look all upset? I
Don't know if you saw what happened at betas chat, but you know
Summer just started attacking me. I have people that are my mods
You know if you're my mod you shouldn't be like calling me a grifter
You shouldn't be calling me a scam artist. You should understand that I'm not these things
You shouldn't be well enough to know that I'm not you shouldn't say I'm just after dick and money and stuff like that
I mean, it's like so if you're a mod and saying these things
It's like wow. Why are you a mod? Like it's like I need
Everyone like you know, and it's like you're supposed to my friend. Why are you saying those things like?
it hurts it's like because even like do I consider my best friends in this community and stuff like
that are just hating on me there's still your friends there's still your friends there's ups and
downs with this like you've had many many ups and downs correct um yeah but i mean it's like i've
had like a lot of fun but it's like it's just like it's like i'm having less fun i'm like
You know, but I have to be consistent because it is I'm running a show and yeah, but I do have
Maybe it's it's time to take a timeout even if it's just for a few days
People are people keep bringing things up from like six months ago and like, you know, it's like yeah
I thought maybe it sticks along the way. Sure. Does anybody make mistakes? I started streaming in January
That's when I saw me. I started doing my live panels in January. I started streaming last year
So I've been at this relatively for a short time and it's like, and I know I came out of
Benny's and like, you know, IP two community and it's like, and then I know how some of them
do think of people as low cows and are kind of cruel behind the scenes and stuff like that.
But it's like, even like low cows, it seems to get better treatment than I do. I mean,
it's like, I get treated. I'm not about low cows.
That's how that's how people are people are calling me constantly. That's what I see it constantly
You're just a little coward. We're just here to laugh at you. We're just here to like, you know, you know
I don't think that's true and I deal with little cows Jimmy is my locale
Janet's quickly becoming my number two and I wouldn't put you in that category
I haven't fucked with you like I have the cows
I don't consider myself I don't consider you on either but I what I wouldn't do is even put that out there
Well, why put that into the art are they are putting it out there nor them being said about me I know
But it's being said anyway, and it's like and so you know
I understand like some of the people the audience is like just like you know
They're like make fun of people and stuff, but I see there's some people they respect. I mean they just like love some people
and are kind to some people and in people's chats and it's like and then it's like oh look at that
it's just like i'm just getting so denigrated and it's like and i've helped people i've
helped people as much as i can i said i let anybody can come promote their channel i'd
let you and yes you have to i did not remember when you did donate you know and it was like you
know and maybe to promote your show or whatever but it's like i would have let you promote your
show for free you know it's like it wasn't necessary to to even donate i let everybody
Yeah, and it's like, you know, I don't think you're a bad mod and um
I don't care if I'm a mod or not
And I I hate when people bitching complain about wrenches
Especially when people mod with their feelings like I saw this you me person
Time out half your chat last week and I haven't I used to watch almost every day
So like I don't do that as much anymore, but that will probably change
Uh, and it's mostly it's because I I don't like a lot of your guests, but that doesn't mean they're always gonna be there
Like I kept and I kept saying you allow ghosts to buy this and whatever, you know
And maybe there's some truth to that maybe there's not but I don't think it's always gonna be like that
But I mean I think what where people get frustrated is you know ghost was a heavy-donator, right?
And then
Like I don't want to hold up on it. Let me finish like good, but let me just tell you are cheap ghosts is like
I'm not gonna donate any more because
We're saying I'm gay and I'm getting attacked and someone called my brother and my family
Look his behavior
Look, I came over here and he's sexually harassing
Page and every other female guest people don't want to watch that
Okay, maybe that's true, but it's not always like that and it's great when everyone gets along
You know it like out of some people love Alex some people hate Alex sometimes personally, I like Alex sometimes I don't like them
But they, they're very strong personalities.
Talk about, talk about Alexandra and not Alex McQueen.
Oh, Alex, Alexandra, I do like.
She's got massive balls on her, dude.
She kind of rules in a heated day.
I love her, I love her.
I also like Tommy, so I can like Tommy and like Alex too.
Like, just like I like Q and I like Sam, man.
You don't have to pick sides all the time.
But I'd rather have people that at least come on the show at least like me
I'd like you know, it's like I want to be people do like you
But they see someone like go sexually harass somebody and they blame you for it for allowing it
Good, but ghost is like that's his person that like if you know goes
I know he doesn't mean harm. He doesn't mean harm by it. He was
I kicked them off the panel
Okay, well, it's not everybody's gonna be everybody's favorite, but that's not that's what I was just saying you can't please everybody
I want people to respect my show and me and that's the whole thing. It's like there's like I can't
It's it's too it's getting too much words like people are asking it too much of me and like and then accusing me of like of like trying to like
Donation thing hurt you. Oh, honestly, there's a easy way to fix that
I honestly I would set of rules up front that apply towards everything, right?
I do like RG. They're posted in my description the channel. I know
know they don't but it's like rules don't always get followed and it's like no
matter how many times I've stradded about the panel rules people will still say
the n-word. You let someone throw like 200 and something dollars at you and
that you know will void out a different rule just keep it consistent
And I think
Donate it like some people that have donated a large amount a little bit different and it's like I'm sorry
And that's just the way things are because I don't have that many
Donators and so they stand out people are gonna get frustrated and you're gonna have this happen all over again
Yeah, but he's since missing is better psych. No one's required to yeah
But nobody's required to donate and I just I'm fair with the donations and stuff like that
I don't, I don't, I don't know how I'm applying rules differently to people.
Like, if people, basically, you know, I'll treat people the same and it's like, I treat
people the same.
I, but I'll give people with advice services, I'll let them, you know, give them their money.
You'll let them sexually harass a female panelist for hours and hours.
No for hours and hours. So you're being I'm just telling you what I saw
I'm not attacking you either
But if someone feels sexually harassed, you know, they they feel like you know that they can leave and you know
They don't have to be here. It's exactly what I did is they stopped watching
But I came back
No, no, no, I don't I don't like watching females get harassed. It upsets. Okay. Well, I don't like I don't like I don't like it either
But it's like then again, it's like Paige and
Alexandra
We're like I would kick him off the panel Alexander's like bring him back
I don't care. He'd even say rude things like it's like yes
I believe that the females are strong enough to defend themselves and if they feel harassed and they
You know, they can like either like let me know. Hey
You know get this this is too much like get this guy up or they can like leave and it's like and that's goes for anybody
It's like if you know the door is it no one's forced into like a room with people
I'm not forcing them together and it's like oh, you know, it's like they're here people are here of their own free will
That's what I'm saying. It's like right. It's like that's what I mean
You know and people are gonna they're gonna vote with their views meaning if they don't
Stop watching
Come on calm down a little bit
But like I said, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not the views for me.
It's not, it's not, wow, I have 53.
It is, because if you get under 20, you get really upset.
No, if I'm under 20, if I'm under 20 that are harassing me and stuff, if I have five people that are good and like, I can have a conversation, I'm happy with five people that are good.
If I have a hundred people that are just like, all attacking me, you know, I don't want like a hundred people attacking me.
I'd rather have five people being, you know, being cool and cordial and having fun.
It's not about like, and I don't like people getting harassed. I don't like people being called names.
I have rules, I lay them out, I kick people off, and it's like, you know, I kick ghosts
off, you know, if he goes too far, and it's like, I think that it's like, you know, it's
really
If you think you're being fair and consistent, that's a different story, though.
Right.
I think I'm being...
I don't think...
You're obviously not happy.
You're obviously upset, so you need to figure out what's not working.
Right, and I know I know we're each full but it's like I know I'm not happy because I was just at beta's panel
And I had five people screaming at me like my mods or former mods all screaming at me saying really terrible things
That I'm you know, but I've been told I have HIV
Those people are your friend. Why are we upset with you? Can you figure that out?
Yes, I can figure that out because they were really never my friends like obviously I didn't do anything to them
I didn't do anything to these people. Okay, what is it? Oh, well, you know, you didn't say hi to me and chat
You put me back stage for five minutes. You unmodded me. It was like the stupidest little thing
It's like well, yeah, because I run my show like I want you and it's like what makes the people like you're talking about I don't
Ah
Say they were never your friends. I think there's they still are your friends. They're just upset
Bronze bird. No, like people are saying. Oh, Bronze bird was your support. I never thought
This is a good guy and he was your supporter. No, he wasn't. Yeah, we know he wasn't he one time
He like and I'm not saying okay if you have to donate to be a supporter, but like, yeah
Oh, he donated. He donated. Yeah, he donated six months ago to have 40 diamond
I will see I don't I've also brought like I did
Even when I was mad at him I yeah, but people are for the right reasons even when I was mad at him
I said hey, I was like, you know, go check out his channel. Go support him. Don't be trolling
Don't be mean to him, you know, and that's what I say about everybody. Go ahead
I play I've seen so many people say no outside promotion. No, like that's like maybe
That's a smart thing to do, because it's like people have just taken advantage of it.
You love people doing that, and it's great.
Right, and people have come in here and they said, oh, well, I'm live right now, come to my live, right?
And people have actually said that, right?
I've seen you send people over to other people's lives.
I've seen you do that many times.
I will my point is something isn't working right now, right?
Your friends in the audience friend. I don't care what you say
It's fine. It's the community. It's the community. It's the community. It's like I honestly
And figure it out. Thank you. Well, thank you for your advice. I appreciate you and thank you for being
Yumi is a fucking weirdo and I would keep her far away, but again, it's your it's your channel
Uh, I I'm watching her randomly pick fights with people people. She makes people feel uncomfortable
Uh, and you were talking about locale behavior
She's a good example of it to be honest with you. All right. Have a
I haven't seen this tourism or horrendous. This is his own baggage, right?
Bronzeberg was never supported. He only joins for cursing and lure viewers to his panel. That's not true because uh
Bronzeberg has been here for a while
Uh and you're using your personal bias to try to manipulate
So brosberg hasn't been here for months. He's a beat, you know
I only see my beat his channel and then he came here last night to just book and show
He used to watch all the time call me a scammer screaming call me a scammer
Call me a jifter bringing up emma bringing up a lisa saying oh, they don't want to fuck with you
You are people's opinions change you why are they changing?
Maybe you're right, dude, maybe it's everyone else, you know
Take care you means the fucking weirdo. That's all later. Okay. Well, see yeah, and it's like is that considerable now
Now Yumi's gonna be like, oh you were letting my cat and she's not gonna say that right, but it's like, you know, it's like my like
just people say things and am I responsible for that?
And I know I'm just using that example, right?
It's like, I can't control
when people say on their way out sometimes, right?
Like, and so, but he wanted to say
that on the way out, right?
And so, you know, I don't have a, like basically, you know,
I didn't like some of the racial stuff
and I don't like racial stuff.
I, I, guys, I do test racism, I do test homophobia.
I'm a gay man.
Look, if you see the homophobia,
I put up with them this panel,
like my on this channel, right?
this is like is there any gay man that will that will uh put up with that i mean besides me
i can't think of any i can't think of any i can't think of a gay man that was like hey
you can go ahead say f a ggoz and that's what i i did allow that for several until i got monetized
i would allow that i was like that word doesn't offend me because i i don't take it as personal
I don't like it when it's like, you know, said because it's against TOS and it's and stuff like that, right?
And so that's why I said don't say that. I mean, it's like, but you know, I don't care if people are constantly saying the N word
Oh soft a hard ER. They're black. They're allowed to say it. They're you know, so but I'm not allowed to say anything
Okay
Anyway, I don't want to I don't want this to be like a you know, big cry session. I'm just gonna say
I'm here, I love you guys, most of you, you know who you are that hate me, and it's like
if you hate me, I just don't regard you, okay?
It's like, you have something to say, you don't have to shame me publicly, yell at me
Seems like really mean spirited. I guess people do hate me and it's fine. It's fine. It's fine
Because I I guess I asked for it, right somewhere. I asked for it, right? I just asked to be hated, right?
I asked to be hated, denigrated, you know, I asked for, you know, anybody that supports me to be told
Oh, you're just sucking his dick, you know, you know
Yeah, I asked for my donators to be harassed. I asked for that, right?
I didn't ask for that. I don't want it. I've really tried to have people like, you know, give people chances to get along and stuff like that.
I've really tried. And it's like, what? Well, what, you know, at this point.
What?
Maybe if everyone hates me, then I'll just go away